[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
The case against me is dismissed.
I will be going back to the capitol
to claim my rightful title
as governor of Ardiente.
[woman] Lily Cruz did book a flight.
[Helena] So, what are you waiting for?
I have a concert to do tonight.
Do not disturb me.
Go after Lily Cruz!
[Julio] Arnaldo! What happened to you?
Lily said I killed her Nanny Carlotta.
Am I a bad person?
[Julio] No. You are not a bad person.
It's time for you to come home.
You'll come to the mansion
whether you like it or not.
And suspiciously,
why isn't Lily Cruz here?
Piece of advice.
Don't believe that she's leaving
because Lily Cruz never flees.
And more importantly, she never dies.
The Dragon Ladies have been
arrested by the police.
[Mercedes] They are questioning
them about you.
They know you're Red Dragon.
[Emilia] Tonight we are
celebrating the anniversary
of Helena Montoya's foundation.
[Helena] This night is especially
for the people of Ardiente.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I recognize the one, the only…
[Lily] Lily Cruz.
[Myla] And I guarantee you that Red Dragon
is none other than Helena Montoya.
[Lily] Everyone here knows
that Helena Montoya
is none other than Red Dragon.
Oh, Helena, sorry. The show is over
because the whole world
now knows your secret, Red Dragon.
Me? "Red Dragon"?
Careful with your accusations.
My lawyers can sue you for libel.
You've got no evidence, Lily Cruz.
You knew about this, didn't you?
I don't know what you're talking about!
We aren't done yet.
Don't point fingers without proof.
Red Dragon will still trust me
because I'm more useful.
-You bastard!
-Yeah?
Drop the act, Helena.
You want evidence?
I don't just accuse people without proof.
Here.
Bank statements.
Oh, maybe you missed this.
Does it look familiar?
It's your blue book.
And these are papers proving
that your business is illegal.
And I also have the list
of people you wanted dead
after this special occasion.
Do you want to know who's
on Red Dragon's hit list?
Topping her list is none other
than Salvador Tatad.
[Helena] That's not true.
[Lily] Isagani Bacaro.
[Helena] No.
Leticia Hidalgo. Horacio Perez.
-That is not true!
-[Lily] It'd actually take us
all night if I read
the whole list, so I'll stop.
But if some of you are still wondering,
well, you'd better believe it.
I myself was duped.
We were all conned by Helena Montoya.
She pretended to love us,
but the truth is,
we were merely playthings in her schemes.
I'm not doing anything illegal,
but you certainly are.
I'll sue you for libel!
Are you sure you're clean?
Here.
See for yourself, Helena!
What are these? Photoshopped!
-These are fake!
-[Lily laughs]
They're fake! They were photoshopped!
They will never hold in court!
You're the fake.
I am Helena Montoya!
I'm a philanthropist.
I help the poor.
I will not allow someone
like Lily Cruz to slander me.
[sighs]
Sorry. This Lily Cruz just did it.
Oh! And in case you were wondering,
the authorities already have
copies of the evidence I have.
Hi, sir!
[Lily] Aww. They're about to arrest you.
Helena Montoya, you are under
arrest for arms trafficking
and human trafficking.
[Agent Asuncion] Let's go.
-Please come with us.
-Let go of me!
-Wait! You cannot do this to my mama!
-Don't touch me!
This isn't over.
She hasn't done anything!
And you! You little witch!
Who do you think you are, huh?
You cannot do this to my mama!
Why, Emilia?
Are you jealous of your mother?
Do you want to join her in jail?
You don't belong there.
I have other plans for you.
This isn't over!
You've got that right…
-…because you're next!
-We'll never be over!
I'll make sure you'll be done for, Emilia.
-[Anna] Aunt Camia.
-Anna.
Helena Montoya is being arrested.
Thank goodness! How's Lily? Is she safe?
Don't worry. Lily's doing fine.
[ominous music]
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
Boss Jaguar, they're arresting
Madam Red Dragon.
We're moving in.
-Don't.
-Boss…
If we won't do something,
Madam will be behind bars.
Use your damn head.
By meddling, you'll only
make her look suspicious.
Back off now.
And that is an order.
Back off!
Boss Jaguar wants us to back off.
-What?
-Just back off! Let's go!
I know how much it will pain
you if Lily gets hurt.
I won't let that happen.
You'll never have to worry again, Camia.
-It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
-The mother and her daughter…
both taken down by a wildflower.
How do you like that?
[Julio sighs]
-Wait. Wait!
-It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
-Let's go.
-It's gonna be fine.
-[Julio] Oh.
-Bye, Helena.
You!
Yes? Well?
Mama!
Wait. Why are they arresting my grandma?
What is Lily doing here?
You really don't remember
anything about that woman?
Don't you remember her…
doing something like this to you?
The same thing she did to your grandma.
You mean that she also had me arrested?
I have to go.
Where are you off to?
I have to clear up things about my past.
[tense music swelling]
[Magbanua] Should we
follow your grandson, sir?
No, no. It's okay, Magbanua.
If it's the truth he seeks…
let's hope it's the truth he finds.
Lily Cruz.
You are something else.
[scoffs]
Let's go.
Good night.
If a bunch of demons like the Ardientes
couldn't bring me down,
what makes you think an old dragon can?
Checkmate, Helena Montoya.
You just got slayed.
Where were you?
I've been looking all over
for you. Where did you go?
I just went to the washroom.
What washroom?
Mama just got arrested,
and you weren't even there.
-You're so worthless.
-No…
No. That's what I want to know.
What happened? What did Lily Cruz do?
I heard she exposed something?
That woman has always been a troublemaker.
She's done nothing but try
to ruin my family.
First, it was Arnaldo,
then Papa, and now, Mama!
-Speak of the devil and she comes!
-Emilia.
How dare you show your face
here after what you did!
Shut your trap,
I didn't come here for you.
I'm just making sure that
Red Dragon stays in her cage.
Oh, come on, Lily Cruz.
Don't savor your victory
because it's not over yet.
Once Mama gets out, I'll--
What? Have me killed? Raped?
Buried alive again?
Didn't you try all that already?
But you failed each time,
Emilia. Each time.
While I've managed
to do everything I said I would.
Because I make sure I get the job done.
So, you better be afraid,
Emilia. Be very afraid.
Calm down, Emilia.
You know what? I've already said enough.
I need my lawyer present.
Let's go, Emilia.
[Raul] Emilia.
Mama, I already warned you
about Lily Cruz,
but you didn't believe me.
You're a powerful woman,
and yet you still fell
for her booby traps.
Yes.
I underestimated her. I let my guard down.
But it's okay. I'll play her little game.
Let's see which one of us
raises the white flag first.
Looks like you have something
planned for Lily Cruz.
Like you said, baby girl,
your mama is a very powerful woman.
I am above the law.
No, wait, I am the law.
And that Lily Cruz just declared
a full-fledged war against Red Dragon.
Thanks, Diego. I couldn't have
done this without you.
Thank you for everything you've done
to help take Helena down.
This isn't over yet, Lily.
And I can't leave Red Dragon's group
until she's definitely behind bars.
I know that, Diego.
And that's why I'm so worried about you.
You're doing something
dangerous for me. For us.
And that's why I want you out of there.
Out of Red Dragon's turf.
But don't worry.
I'll get you out of there real soon.
Don't you worry.
I can take care of myself.
What matters is that
Red Dragon doesn't get away.
She has to pay for all her crimes.
Thanks again, Diego.
[soft music playing]
[exhales heavily]
You've been standing there
for ages, Emilia.
I think it'd be much better
if you just relax,
and not think about
your mother for a while.
Because I'm sure she's innocent, right?
I mean, she ought to be, right?
You know, Raul? Can you just shut up?
Don't think I've forgotten that
you left when Mama got arrested.
To the men's room? I had to go, okay?
I had to answer the call of nature.
-Yeah, right, Raul.
-No. You know what…
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Do you two know I can hear you both
from all the way in my bathroom?
I was about to take a bath.
But then, I didn't know the show
from earlier had a sequel.
You should've told me so I
could've ordered some popcorn.
Oh, no, we were just…
And you, Papa.
You think I forgot?
You didn't even try to help Mama.
[Julio] Emilia.
Lily Cruz and I have our own little war.
And I don't want to get dragged
into her fight with your mother.
Besides, you saw what
happened, right? There.
Your amazing mother has fallen.
And this is what I've been
telling you all along.
You bet on the wrong horse.
Or, should I say,
you bet on the wrong dragon?
But then again, you're a very lucky girl.
Because your father is here.
And he's back on top.
I am, once again, in power.
Well then, I'll leave you two lovebirds
to iron out your problems.
Get a room.
[door closes]
Lily, I'm really happy that you and Diego
were finally able to expose Red Dragon.
I really hope that's the end of her
so that they can't hurt any more people.
But this battle isn't over, Mom.
We can't let our guard down
until Helena Montoya
is sentenced and truly put behind bars.
Why? Do you think
she has that many connections?
Like the members in her syndicate?
It's not just that.
I know how people like Helena work.
She can have her crimes absolved,
or escape from the law.
But I'll be one step ahead of her.
I'll take down whatever
plan she has in store.
-Michelle?
-Governor.
What happened?
We were transferred
to a different department.
-Who ordered it?
-Julio Ardiente, sir.
He said you aren't the governor anymore.
We've ironed everything out
while you were away, Governor.
We've silenced everyone
who was against you.
I can safely say that this town is yours.
Once again, you're the king now, sir.
-I like your style, Magbanua.
-Thank you, sir.
And I hope that you'll always
bring me news like this.
-Always good news.
-[sighs]
Well, that's the thing.
Since you were on vacation,
Red Dragon was still able to acquire
all of your gambling dens
here in Tierra del Viento.
And I thought Lily Cruz clipped
the wings of that dragon.
I thought she was already rotting in jail.
Never mind.
Anyway, this is what we'll do.
Let us make sure we regain everything
that was taken from me.
And this time, let's make sure…
that what is mine remains mine alone.
Especially Poblacion Ardiente.
Because that place has
a very special spot in my heart.
Watch, Magbanua.
Watch as my plans unfold
before your very eyes.
They haven't seen nothing yet.
Oh!
[chuckles]
Look what the cat dragged in.
Good morning, Vice Governor Mateo Ruiz.
How can I be of service to you?
What you're doing is illegal, Julio.
The law has yet to decide
on your reinstatement.
I can still have you arrested.
But I'll allow you a chance to leave.
[groans]
Vice, are you challenging
your duly elected
and newly-reinstated governor
of Tierra del Viento, huh?
Don't ask for trouble.
The law is on my side.
I'm still the governor
of Tierra del Viento.
[scoffs] There's a flaw in your law.
[Julio chuckles]
Or do you mean, Red Dragon,
your secret boss?
Your master is done, and so are you.
So, if I were you, you should
just step down as vice governor,
and leave this place quietly.
Make sure no one hears you.
That would do you a lot better. Hmm?
Security, take this old man outside.
[Magbanua] Ah, ah, ah.
[Julio] Oh.
You're really hot under the collar, Mateo.
But it looks like your boys
are outnumbered by mine.
Magbanua, will you please escort
Vice Governor Mateo Ruiz?
Take the trash outside.
Take him…
That looks better. You're more relaxed.
[speaking in Spanish] Hot. Hot, Mateo.
See you when I see you.
[chuckles]
Nobody but nobody beats Julio Ardiente.
[sighs]
-[woman 1] We've got our time…
-[woman 2] So when?
What are we still doing here?
Aren't we going to help Red Dragon?
We have a plan, Boss Diego.
We're just waiting
for Mercedes' go-signal.
She and Emilia are the only ones
Red Dragon has spoken to.
This mission is in full force.
You and your group
should prepare yourselves.
All right, ma'am.
I'll leave you here to talk.
Don't worry.
I switched off the surveillance.
Well done.
Your guards are so obedient, Mama.
[Helena] They should be.
Staying here isn't cheap.
So, you mean to say, Mama,
you have people in the agency?
[Helena] Of course I have
connections everywhere, Emilia.
We're only given 10 minutes.
So, let's begin.
Okay.
I'm going to move camps tomorrow,
so you need to intercept
the transport vehicle
before we leave the site.
Yes, Madam.
We'll take a detour here, which
gives us a few minutes advantage
before the enemy gets to us.
Then I'll disperse our people,
so we won't have any setbacks
and your escape will be smooth.
[Helena] Yes. That's good.
Don't worry, Mama. I'll review her plans
before execution,
so Mercedes doesn't screw up.
What are you trying to say, Emilia?
Enough!
Emilia is right.
I haven't punished you
for your many failures yet.
You're the reason why I'm here,
and you will get me out.
You are one of my most trusted servants,
so I'll give you another chance.
Don't waste this opportunity.
Is that understood, Mercedes?
Yes, Madam. I won't let you down.
As I was saying, ladies,
if you were paying full attention earlier,
this is where they'll be
taking Red Dragon.
This is where you'll be waiting.
And this is where you'll intercept them.
And then what?
Where will we take her?
Who's going to help her escape?
Just focus on your mission.
We'll take care of the rest.
If you want this to succeed,
then you'll have to tell me
every single detail.
And that includes all the
Red Dragon's possible routes.
The Madam specifically said
to limit the information
available to those who
will be joining this mission.
It seems like she doesn't
trust that many people.
Not even her ally, such as yourself.
Lily, I already asked them to make dinner.
It's fine, Mom.
I'm not really in the mood
to eat right now.
I keep thinking about Diego.
I'm still worried because
every minute he's out there,
he's risking his life in the syndicate
just so he can help me fight Red Dragon.
Diego's doing all this
because he loves you.
Anyone would do anything
for the one they love.
Yes, I know.
And that's why I want to end this.
Not just for our family,
or for the people of Ardiente,
but for Diego too.
I'm the reason why he's still in there.
Now, I want to make sure
he gets out of there alive.
I hope the day comes
when we can finally be happy.
When we can finally live in peace.
The day when we can all be free.
I hope so too, dear.
I'll pray it comes true.
[soft music playing]
I know how much it'll pain you
if Lily gets hurt.
I won't let that happen.
This is where they'll be taking
Red Dragon,
while this is where Diego
and the others will be waiting.
So, you'll be intercepting him here,
because this is the last part
of the route that he knows.
Then, we'll go straight ahead
until Red Dragon
finally manages to escape here.
And then, we drive
all the way to the suburbs.
Do you understand?
Whatever it is you're planning
to help Red Dragon escape,
I'll make sure it fails.
[tense music swelling]
[bright music playing]
Anna!
-Anna, we're back.
-[Anna] Jepoy.
-Did you bring my fruits?
-[Jepoy] Here it is.
These pineapples look so sweet.
They're definitely sweet.
We actually brought four, but
Marlon and I already ate one.
-Sorry about that.
-Wait. Have some water.
You must be tired. Here.
Anna, look at these huge coconuts I got.
These are good.
Oh, thank you, Marlon.
Could you peel some for us?
Sure. Batch told me
to take care of you. Wait here.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Did you wait long?
-No. Look, you're all sweaty.
-You sure you didn't?
-Not really.
Let's have some of these. I'll peel them.
Okay.
Jepoy, I really hope
Lily and Aunt Camia are safe.
Now that they put Red Dragon behind bars…
I'm afraid she'll get back at them.
You shouldn't worry too much
about them, okay?
Diego and Lily are there
to protect Aunt Camia.
Come here.
Don't you like it here?
It's quiet.
We have all the time for each other.
We're at peace here.
Don't you agree?
Jepoy, we didn't go with Lily
to face Red Dragon
because we need to focus
on Arnaldo, remember?
Because he chose to go with the Ardientes.
Arnaldo?
[tense music playing]
Agent Salonga, again,
I'd like to thank you
and the entire team for
helping me catch Red Dragon.
No problem, Miss Cruz.
In fact, we should be
thanking you instead.
If it weren't for the evidence
you gave us,
we probably wouldn't
have caught Red Dragon.
Thank you.
But, I have to warn you, Agent Salonga.
I know what Red Dragon is capable of.
She'll do everything to drop
the charges against her.
[tense music playing]
One more thing, you have to keep your ears
and your eyes wide open at all times.
Why?
Because Red Dragon's men
can infiltrate even the NBI.
Just saying.
[tense music intensifies]
[Anna] Arnaldo?
Are you all right?
I'm confused about a lot of things.
I have so many questions.
But I don't have answers.
Who exactly is Ivy Aguas?
The woman I know as Ivy Aguas,
why do you call her Lily?
Well?
I don't understand, who…
Who's Nanny Carlotta? Why did I kill her?
Why did I kill someone?
Well?
I don't understand… I have
so many questions in my head.
But I don't have the answers.
And nobody's giving me answers.
No one! Not you… or you! Nobody!
Especially you.
What are you hiding from me?
-Answer me!
-Arnaldo!
Why don't you just forget
about everything, Arnaldo?!
It won't do you or any of us any good!
[somber music playing]
This is your chance to start over.
So you shouldn't throw it away.
Arnaldo. Hey.
Did he hurt you? Are you okay?
[action music playing]
[reporter] As of right now,
we're told that Helena Montoya is being
transferred to a new prison camp.
The philanthropist is accused of being
the syndicate leader "Red Dragon."
The transfer is to ensure that she is kept
safe against any attempts on her life.
Now, let's see how far
your wings will take you,
my beloved Red Dragon.
[phone ringing]
[ominous music swells]
Camia, sorry, I didn't tell you earlier.
Something important came up.
It's okay, Damian.
Whatever it is, take care.
Is Lily there?
That's what I'm worried about.
She's with the NBI right now.
They'll make sure that there
won't be any problems
with Red Dragon's transfer.
Tell her that somebody tipped me off.
Red Dragon's planning something big.
What do you mean?
What is she planning?
That's all I heard, Camia.
Just tell Lily to be careful.
-All right, Damian. Thank you.
-Bye.
-Let's go, Camacho.
-Yes, boss.
[tense music playing]
[sensual music playing]
Hey…
Daddy.
[Mercedes] Mr. Oscar. The Madam
is quite busy at the moment.
But I can set an appointment
so you two can talk.
I'm so glad you could join me.
I have something for you.
You made it. What's that?
Is that champagne?
-Yup.
-Hmm.
I'm glad you're home.
-For you.
-So sweet of you.
I have a great idea.
Why don't you join me?
Maybe later. I still have
things to take care of.
I know, Daddy. It's because you're sad.
Because Red Dragon is
now exposed, and she got caught.
And now that she's in jail,
that only means one thing.
That power in your group
is up for grabs, right?
And you know I love a man in power.
And…
I want you to be the most
powerful man of them all.
Why don't you give me a nice scrub, Daddy?
Sure.
I missed you so much, Daddy.
I missed you too.
You are my key to Red Dragon's kingdom.
You'll be getting me into that syndicate.
And once I'm in, I can have
everything I want and more.
I'm going to get back
at every single person who ruined my life.
Thank you, Daddy.
[action music playing]
Your Uncle Damian got a tip that
Red Dragon's up to something.
[phone dings]
I'M READY, MOM. THANK YOU.
Romulo.
-Sir!
-[gunshot]
[laughs]
[phone ringing]
Yes?
Good job, Romulo.
Good job, huh?
Oh. That's one of our men.
Damn it. Follow them.
[action music playing]
[tires screeching]
Criminals!
Get ready!
[tires screeching]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[phone ringing]
Diego?
Lily, get ready. She's on her way.
I will. Thank you, Diego.
Thank you very much.
Here's the route Red Dragon's convoy
will take when she escapes.
Be on the alert, and be careful.
Diego, thank you. Thank you for this.
We're going to surprise Red Dragon.
She won't know what's coming.
And she won't get away.
[action music playing]
How did they know we were here?
How did they learn about our route?
Helena Montoya, get out of the car!
Get out! Get out!
[gunshot]
Hey! Men, duck!
[tires screeching]
[gunshots]
[gunfire continues]
[gunshot]
-[gunshots]
-Hurry!
[gunshots]
[car engine revving]
[tires screech]
[gunshots]
[helicopter thrumming]
[gunshot]
[gunshot ]
[gunshots]
[helicopter thrumming]
[tense musing playing]
[action music playing]
[Helena laughing]
Open the door!
-Open the door!
-Oh, Lily Cruz.
[laughs]
Oh my. Pathetic.
-Open it!
-[laughs]
Helena!
Bye-bye.
[helicopter thrumming]
[Helena laughing]
Bye, Lily Cruz.
[Helena] Oh, my gosh.
So pathetic.
[action music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
You know, Agent Salonga,
I'd be careful if I were you.
I think my suspicions are correct.
There's a snake amongst us.
The Big Four want to set a meeting.
Big Four? And who the hell are they?
They are the four leaders of
Red Dragon's operations
in the north, south, east, and west
areas of the country.
Shouldn't we be talking about
who's going to replace Red Dragon?
It's quite obvious that I should take
Red Dragon's place
since I'm her only daughter.
Why don't we have an election?
Emilia versus me
for Red Dragon's position.
[theme music playing]